A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1924-1939 FA308
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1932
  - International, 1932; 1932/100
    - International - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1932; 1932/100.D
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1932 (Box 65, Folder 530)
    - International - Hookworm, 1932; 1932/100.H
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1932 (Box 65, Folder 530)
    - International - Malaria, 1932; 1932/100.I
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1932 (Box 65, Folder 531)
    - International - Yellow Fever, 1932; 1932/100.O
      - Staff Communications and International Affairs, 1932 (Box 65, Folder 531)
  - United States, 1932; 1932/200
    - United States - (A-M), 1932 (Box 65, Folder 532)
    - United States - (N-S), 1932 (Box 65, Folder 533)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/200.E
      - United States - (A-F), 1932 (Box 66, Folder 535)
      - United States - (H-R), 1932 (Box 66, Folder 536)
      - Not Used (Box 66, Folder 537)
      - United States - (S-Z), 1931 (Box 66, Folder 538)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1932; 1932/200.A
      - United States - (T-Z), 1932 (Box 65, Folder 534)
      - United States, 1932 (Box 66, Folder 535)
    - United States - Public Health Demonstrations, 1932; 1932/200.J
      - United States, 1932 (Box 66, Folder 538)
    - United States - Health Services, 1932; 1932/200.K
      - United States, 1932 (Box 66, Folder 538)
    - United States - Public Health Education, 1932; 1932/200.L
      - United States - Cincinnati Institute, 1932 (Box 66, Folder 539)
      - United States - Cincinnati Institute - Miscellaneous, 1932 (Box 66, Folder 540)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1932; 1932/200.S
      - United States, 1932 (Box 66, Folder 541)
  - Alabama, 1932; 1932/201
    - Alabama, 1932 (Box 66, Folder 542)
    - Alabama - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/201.E
      - Alabama, 1932 (Box 66, Folder 542)
  - Arizona, 1932; 1932/203
    - Arizona - State Board of Health, 1932 (Box 66, Folder 542)
    - Arizona, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 543)
    - Arizona - Public Health Education, 1932; 02.1932/203.L
      - Arizona, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 543)
    - Arizona - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/203.E
      - Arizona, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 543)
  - Arkansas, 1932; 1932/204
    - Arkansas, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 545)
    - Arkansas - State Board of Health, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 544)
    - Arkansas - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/204.E
      - Arkansas, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 545)
  - California, 1932; 1932/205
    - California - State Board of Health, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 546)
    - California, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 547)
    - California - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/205.E
      - California, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 547)
  - Panama Canal Zone, 1932; 1932/206
    - Panama Canal Zone - Nursing, 1932; 1932/206.C
      - Panama Canal Zone, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 548)
  - Colorado, 1932; 1932/207
    - Colorado, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 548)
  - Connecticut, 1932; 1932/208
    - Connecticut, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 548)
  - Florida, 1932; 1932/211
    - Florida, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 548)
    - Florida - Public Health Education, 1932; 1932/211.L
      - Florida, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 548)
  - Georgia, 1932; 1932/212
    - Georgia, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 549)
  - Hawaii, 1932; 1932/214
    - Hawaii, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 550)
    - Hawaii - Social Sciences, 1932; 1932/214.S
      - Hawaii, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 550)
  - Idaho, 1932; 1932/215
    - Idaho, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 550)
  - Illinois, 1932; 1932/216
    - Illinois, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 551)
  - Indiana, 1932; 1932/217
    - Indiana, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 552)
  - Iowa, 1932; 1932/218
    - Iowa, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 552)
  - Kansas, 1932; 1932/219
    - Kansas, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 552)
  - Kentucky, 1932; 1932/220
    - Kentucky, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 553)
    - Kentucky, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 555)
    - Kentucky - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/220.E
      - Kentucky, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 553)
  - Louisiana, 1932; 1932/221
    - Louisiana - State Board of Health, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 554)
  - Maine, 1932; 1932/222
    - Maine, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 555)
  - Maryland, 1932; 1932/223
    - Maryland, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 555)
  - Michigan, 1932; 1932/225
    - Michigan, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 555)
  - Minnesota, 1932; 1932/226
    - Minnesota, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 555)
  - Mississippi, 1932; 1932/227
    - Mississippi - State Board of Health, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 556)
    - Mississippi - State Board of Health, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 557)
    - Mississippi - State Board of Health, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 558)
    - Mississippi - State Board of Health, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 559)
    - Mississippi - Nursing, 1932; 1932/227.C
      - Mississippi, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 560)
    - Mississippi, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 560)
    - Mississippi - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/227.E
      - Mississippi, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 560)
    - Mississippi - Public Health Education, 1932; 1932/227.L
      - Mississippi, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 560)
  - Missouri, 1932; 1932/228
    - Missouri, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 561)
    - Missouri - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/228.E
      - Missouri, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 561)
  - Montana, 1932; 1932/229
    - Montana, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 562)
    - Montana - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/229.E
      - Montana, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 562)
    - Montana - Tuberculosis, 1932; 1932/229.T
      - Montana, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 562)
  - Nebraska, 1932; 1932/230
    - Nebraska, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 563)
  - Nevada, 1932; 1932/231
    - Nevada, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 563)
  - New Jersey, 1932; 1932/233
    - New Jersey, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 563)
  - New Mexico, 1932; 1932/234
    - New Mexico, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 563)
  - North Carolina, 1932; 1932/236
    - North Carolina - State Board of Health, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 564)
    - North Carolina - State Board of Health, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 565)
    - North Carolina - State Board of Health - (A-Z), 1932 (Box 69, Folder 566)
    - North Carolina - Milam, Dr. Frank, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 567)
    - North Carolina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/236.E
      - North Carolina, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 567)
    - North Carolina - Yellow Fever, 1932; 1932/236.O
      - North Carolina, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 567)
  - North Dakota, 1932; 1932/237
    - North Dakota, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 568)
  - Ohio, 1932; 1932/238
    - Ohio, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 568)
  - Oklahoma, 1932; 1932/239
    - Oklahoma, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 568)
  - Oregon, 1932; 1932/240
    - Oregon, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 569)
  - Pennsylvania, 1932; 1932/241
    - Pennsylvania, 1932 (Box 69, Folder 569)
  - Rhode Island, 1932; 1932/244
    - Rhode Island, 1932 (Box 70, Folder 570)
    - Rhode Island - Medical Sciences, 1932; 1932/244.A
      - Rhode Island - Butler College, 1932 (Box 70, Folder 570)
  - South Carolina, 1932; 1932/246
    - South Carolina - State Board of Health, 1932 (Box 70, Folder 571)
    - South Carolina, 1932 (Box 70, Folder 572)
    - South Carolina - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/246.E
      - South Carolina, 1932 (Box 70, Folder 572)
  - South Dakota, 1932; 1932/247
    - South Dakota, 1932 (Box 70, Folder 572)
  - Tennessee, 1932; 1932/248
    - Tennessee - State Board of Health - (A-Z) - Milam, Dr. Frank, 1932 (Box 70, Folder 573)
  - Texas, 1932; 1932/249
    - Texas, 1932 (Box 70, Folder 574)
  - Utah, 1932; 1932/250
    - Utah, 1932 (Box 70, Folder 574)
  - Vermont, 1932; 1932/251
    - Vermont, 1932 (Box 70, Folder 574)
  - Virginia, 1932; 1932/252
    - Virginia - State Board of Health, 1932 (Box 70, Folder 575)
    - Virginia, 1932 (Box 70, Folder 576)
    - Virginia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/252.E
      - Virginia, 1932 (Box 70, Folder 576)
  - Washington, 1932; 1932/253
    - Washington, 1932 (Box 70, Folder 576)
    - Washington - Public Health Education, 1932; 1932/253.L
      - Washington, 1932 (Box 70, Folder 576)
  - West Virginia, 1932; 1932/254
    - West Virginia - State Board of Health - (A-Z), 1932 (Box 70, Folder 577)
    - West Virginia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Award, 1932; 1932/254.E
      - West Virginia, 1932 (Box 70, Folder 577)
  - Wisconsin, 1932; 1932/255
    - Wisconsin, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 578)
  - Wyoming, 1932; 1932/256
    - Wyoming, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 578)
    - Wyoming - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/256.E
      - Wyoming, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 578)
  - Virgin Islands, 1932; 1932/257
    - Virgin Islands, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 578)
    - Virgin Islands - Nursing, 1932; 1932/257.C
      - Virgin Islands, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 578)
    - Virgin Islands - Malaria, 1932; 1932/257.I
      - Virgin Islands, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 578)
  - South America, 1932; 1932/300
    - South America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/300.E
      - South America, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 579)
  - Argentina, 1932; 1932/301
    - Argentina, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 579)
    - Argentina - Medical Sciences, 1932; 1932/301.A
      - Argentina, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 579)
    - Argentina - Yellow Fever, 1932; 1932/301.O
      - Argentina, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 579)
  - Bolivia, 1932; 1932/303
    - Bolivia - Yellow Fever, 1932; 1932/303.O
      - Bolivia, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 579)
  - Colombia, 1932; 1932/311
    - Colombia - Bevier, Dr. George, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 580)
    - Colombia, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 581)
    - Colombia - Public Health Education, 1932; 1932/311.L
      - Colombia, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 581)
    - Colombia - Yellow Fever, 1932; 1932/311.O
      - Case Histories, Yellow Fever - Vol. 2 - CAS-1, 1932 (Box 557, Folder 3767)
      - SAN-1 Bauer, Johannes and Kerr, J. Austin "Santa Maria Yellow Fever Investigation" Vol. 2, 1932 (Box 557, Folder 3768)
      - SAN-4 Ramsey, George H. "Fever with Jaundice in Santa Maria" Report and Appendix, 1932 (Box 557, Folder 3769)
  - Costa Rica, 1932; 1932/313
    - Costa Rica - Public Health Demonstrations, 1932; 1932/313.J
      - Costa Rica (Box 71, Folder 581)
    - Costa Rica - Health Services, 1932; 02.1932/313.K
      - Costa Rica, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 581)
    - Costa Rica - Yellow Fever, 1932; 1932/313.O
      - Costa Rica, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 581)
  - Cuba, 1932; 1932/315
    - Cuba, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 581)
  - Guatemala, 1932; 1932/319
    - Guatemala, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 581)
  - Mexico, 1932; 1932/323
    - Mexico, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 582)
    - Mexico - Health Services, 1932; 1932/323.K
      - Mexico, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 582)
  - Nicaragua, 1932; 1932/325
    - Nicaragua, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 583)
  - Panama, 1932; 1932/327
    - Panama, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 583)
  - Paraguay, 1932; 1932/329
    - Paraguay, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 584)
    - Paraguay - Yellow Fever, 1932; 1932/329.O
      - Paraguay, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 584)
  - Peru, 1932; 1932/331
    - Peru, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 584)
    - Peru - Tuberculosis, 1932; 1932/331.T
      - Peru, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 584)
  - El Salvador, 1932; 02.1932/333
    - El Salvador, 1932 (Box 71, Folder 584)
  - Venezuela, 1932; 1932/339
    - Venezuela - Elmendorf, Dr. John E., 1932 (Box 72, Folder 585)
    - Venezuela, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 586)
    - Venezuela - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/339.E
      - Venezuela, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 586)
  - Great Britain, 1932; 1932/400
    - Great Britain, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 587)
  - England, 1932; 1932/401
    - England - (A-M), 1932 (Box 72, Folder 587)
    - England - (N-Z), 1932 (Box 72, Folder 588)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1932; 1932/401.A
      - England, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 588)
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/401.E
      - England, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 588)
      - England - Humanities and Arts, 1932; 1932/401.R
        - England, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 588)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1932; 1932/401.S
      - England, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 588)
  - Ireland, 1932; 1932/403
    - Ireland - Public Health Education, 1932; 1932/403.L
    - Ireland - Health Services, 1932; 1932/403.K
  - Scotland, 1932; 1932/405
    - Scotland, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 589)
    - Scotland - Medical Sciences, 1932; 1932/405.A
      - Scotland, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 589)
  - Australia, 1932; 02.1932/410
    - Australia, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 589)
    - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/410.E
      - Australia, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 589)
  - Queensland, 1932; 1932/412
    - Queensland, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 589)
  - South Australia, 1932; 1932/413
    - South Australia, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 589)
  - New Zealand, 1932; 1932/418
    - New Zealand, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 589)
    - New Zealand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/418.E
      - New Zealand, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 589)
  - British Samoa, 1932; 1932/418.8
    - British Samoa, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 589)
  - Fiji, 1932; 1932/419
    - Fiji, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 590)
  - Caribbean, 1932; 1932/420
    - Caribbean Region - Magoon, E. H. - Malloy, D. M., 1932 (Box 72, Folder 590)
    - Caribbean Region - Malloy, D. M., 1932 (Box 72, Folder 591)
  - Guyana, 1932; 1932/423
    - British Guiana, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 592)
    - Guyana - Hookworm, 1932; 1932/423.H
      - British Guiana, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 592)
    - Guyana - Health Services, 1932; 1932/423.K
      - British Guiana, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 592)
  - Canada, 1932; 1932/427
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1932 (Box 73, Folder 592)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1932; 1932/427.A
      - Canada, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 593)
    - Canada - Public Health Education, 1932; 1932/427.L
      - Canada, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 593)
  - Bahamas, 1932; 1932/433
    - Bahamas, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 594)
  - Jamaica, 1932; 1932/437
    - Jamaica, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 594)
    - Jamaica - Health Services, 1932; 1932/437.K
      - Jamaica, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 594)
  - St. Lucia, 1932; 1932/457
    - St. Lucia - Malaria, 1932; 1932/457.I
      - St. Lucia, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 594)
  - Sri Lanka, 1932; 1932/462
    - Sri Lanka (Ceylon) - Jacocks, W. P., 1932 (Box 73, Folder 595)
  - India, 1932; 1932/464
    - India - (A-Z), 1932 (Box 74, Folder 596)
    - India - Nursing, 1932; 1932/464.C
      - India, 1932 (Box 74, Folder 597)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/464.E
      - India, 1932 (Box 74, Folder 597)
    - India - Public Health Education, 1932; 1932/464.L
      - India, 1932 (Box 74, Folder 597)
    - India (Mysore), 1932; 1932/464.1
      - Mysore, 1932 (Box 74, Folder 598)
      - India (Mysore) - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/464.1E
        - Mysore, 1932 (Box 74, Folder 598)
      - India (Mysore) - Health Services, 1932; 1932/464.1K
        - Mysore, 1932 (Box 74, Folder 598)
        - India (Mysore) - Public Health Education, 1932; 1932/464.1L
          - Mysore, 1932 (Box 74, Folder 598)
    - India (Travancore), 1932; 1932/464.5
      - Travancore, 1932 (Box 74, Folder 598)
      - Travancore, 1932 (Box 74, Folder 598)
      - India (Travancore) - Nursing, 1932; 1932/464.5C
        - Travancore, 1932 (Box 74, Folder 598)
  - Bengal, 1932; 1932/466
    - Bengal, 1932 (Box 74, Folder 598)
  - Burma, 1932; 1932/468
    - Burma - Kendrick, J. F., 1932 (Box 74, Folder 599)
    - Burma - Kendrick, J. F., 1932 (Box 75, Folder 600)
    - Burma - Nursing, 1932; 1932/468.C
      - Burma, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 600)
    - Burma - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/468.E
      - Burma, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 600)
    - Burma - Health Services, 1932; 1932/468.K
      - Burma, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 600)
  - Belize, 1932; 1932/472
    - British New Guinea, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 601)
  - Africa, 1932; 1932/475
    - Africa - Social Sciences, 1932; 1932/475.S
      - Africa, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 601)
  - Mauritius, 1932; 1932/478
    - Maritius, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 601)
  - North Africa Region, 1932; 1932/485
    - Egypt, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 601)
    - North Africa Region - Medical Sciences, 1932; 1932/485.A
      - Egypt, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 601)
    - North Africa Region - Hookworm, 1932; 1932/485.H
      - SCO-5 Scott, J. C. "Data Showing Results of Examinations as Tabulated by Age and Sex Groups for the Various Villages", 1932 (Box 557, Folder 3770)
    - North Africa Region - Health Services, 1932; 1932/485.K
      - Egypt, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 601)
  - South Africa, 1932; 02.1932/487
    - South Africa, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 601)
    - South Africa - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/487.E
      - South Africa, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 601)
  - France, 1932; 1932/500
    - France, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 602)
    - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/500.E
      - France, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 602)
    - France - Health Services, 1932; 1932/500.K
      - France, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 602)
    - France - Undulant Fever, 1932; 1932/500.P
      - France, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 602)
    - France - Social Sciences, 1932; 1932/500.S
      - KIT-1 Kittredge, Tracy B. "Social Sciences in France", 1932 (Box 557, Folder 3771)
  - Senegal, 1932; 1932/531
    - Senegal, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 602)
  - Asia, 1932; 1932/600
    - PH-1 Carpenter, Grace "1932 Summary of Work in the East" (Box 558, Folder 3772)
    - Asia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/600.E
      - Asia, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 602)
  - China, 1932; 1932/601
    - China - Administration, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 603)
    - China - (A-F), 1932 (Box 75, Folder 604)
    - China - Grant, John B., 1932 (Box 75, Folder 605)
    - China - Greene, Roger S. - Gunn, Selskar M., 1932 (Box 75, Folder 606)
    - China - Health - (H-P), 1932 (Box 75, Folder 607)
    - China - Peking Union Medical College - Public Health - (P-Z), 1932 (Box 76, Folder 608)
    - China - Medical Sciences, 1932; 1932/601.A
      - China, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 609)
    - China - Nursing, 1932; 02.1932/601.C
      - China, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 609)
    - China - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1932; 1932/601.D
      - China, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 609)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/601.E
      - China, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 609)
    - China - Malaria, 1932; 1932/601.I
      - China, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 609)
    - China - Health Services, 1932; 1932/601.K
      - China, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 609)
  - Japan, 1932; 1932/609
    - Japan, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 610)
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/609.E
      - Japan, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 610)
  - Thailand, 1932; 1932/617
    - Thailand, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 610)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/617.E
      - Thailand, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 610)
  - Holland, 1932; 1932/650
    - Netherlands, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 610)
    - Holland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/650.E
      - Netherlands, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 610)
  - Sumatra/Dutch West Indies, 1932; 1932/657
    - HYD-2 Hydrick, J. L. Trip to Batavia and Sumatra, 1932 (Box 558, Folder 3773)
  - Europe, 1932; 1932/700
    - Europe - (A-L), 1932 (Box 76, Folder 611)
    - Europe - (M-Z), 1932 (Box 76, Folder 612)
      - Europe - Medical Sciences, 1932; 02.1932/700.A
        - Europe, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 612)
    - Europe - Social Sciences, 1932; 1932/700.S
      - Europe, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 612)
  - Austria, 1932; 1932/705
    - Austria, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 613)
    - Austria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/705.E
      - Austria, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 613)
    - Austria - Social Sciences, 1932; 1932/705.S
      - Austria, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 613)
  - Belgium, 1932; 1932/707
    - Belgium, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 613)
    - Belgium - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/707.E
      - Belgium, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 613)
  - Yugoslavia, 1932; 1932/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 614)
    - Yugoslavia - Nursing, 1932; 1932/710.C
      - Yugoslavia, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 614)
    - Yugoslavia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/710.E
      - Yugoslavia, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 614)
  - Bulgaria, 1932; 1932/711
    - Bulgaria, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 614)
    - Bulgaria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/711.E
      - Bulgaria, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 614)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1932; 1932/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 614)
    - Czechoslovakia - Medical Sciences, 1932; 1932/712.A
      - Czechoslovakia, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 614)
    - Czechoslovakia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/712.E
      - Czechoslovakia, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 614)
  - Estonia, 1932; 1932/714
    - Estonia, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 614)
  - Scandinavia, 1932; 1932/716
    - Scandinavia - Social Sciences, 1932; 1932/716.S
      - Scandinavia, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 614)
  - Germany, 1932; 1932/717
    - Germany, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 615)
    - Germany - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1932; 1932/717.D
      - Germany, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 616)
    - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/717.E
      - Germany, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 617)
    - Germany - Humanities and Arts, 1932; 1932/717.R
      - Germany, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 617)
    - Germany - Social Sciences, 1932; 1932/717.S
      - Germany, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 617)
  - Hungary, 1932; 1932/750
    - Hungary, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 618)
  - Italy, 1932; 1932/751
    - Italy, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 618)
    - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/751.E
      - Italy, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 618)
  - Liberia, 1932; 1932/759
    - Liberia, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 619)
  - Morocco, 1932; 1932/765
    - Morocco - Malaria, 1932; 1932/765.I
      - Morocco, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 619)
  - Norway, 1932; 1932/767
    - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/767.E
      - Norway, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 619)
  - Iran, 1932; 1932/771
    - Iran, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 619)
    - Iran - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/771.E
      - Iran, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 619)
  - Portugal, 1932; 1932/773
    - Portugal, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 619)
    - Portugal - Tuberculosis, 1932; 1932/773.T
      - Portugal, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 619)
  - Romania, 1932; 1932/783
    - Romanial, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 619)
    - Romania - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/783.E
      - Romania, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 619)
  - USSR, 1932; 1932/785
    - U. S. S. R., 1932 (Box 77, Folder 620)
    - USSR - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/785.E
      - U. S. S. R., 1932 (Box 77, Folder 620)
    - USSR - Social Sciences, 1932; 1932/785.S
      - U. S. S. R., 1932 (Box 77, Folder 620)
  - Finland, 1932; 1932/787
    - Finland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/787.E
      - Finland, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 620)
  - Poland, 1932; 1932/789
    - Poland, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 621)
    - Poland - Nursing, 1932; 1932/789.C
      - Poland, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 621)
    - Poland - Social Sciences, 1932; 1932/789.S
      - Poland, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 621)
  - Sweden, 1932; 1932/800
    - Sweden, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 622)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/800.E
      - Sweden, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 622)
    - Sweden - Social Sciences, 1932; 1932/800.S
      - Sweden, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 622)
  - Switzerland, 1932; 1932/803
    - Switzerland, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 622)
    - Switzerland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1932; 1932/803.E
      - Switzerland, 1932 (Box 77, Folder 622)